3dstats.com 2002-12-04

# 3DStats.com - Professional Website statistics in real time

**Privacy Statement:**

3DStats.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate its commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this site; 

**User Information:**

3DStats.com does not acquire or collect any personal information about you. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private properties. 3DStats.com does, however, collect information which is specific to how you use the Internet. 3DStats.com servers note non-personally identifying details such as, but not limited to, the server you are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP you use, the type of browser you use, and your IP address. This information is obtained solely for statistical purposes. 

**For 3DStats.com Registered Members:**

3DStats.com regards all personal information collected from its registered members as completely confidential. This includes personal data provided during registration processes. 

**3DStats.com Code:**

When used on registered members web pages 3DStats.com code will only gather non-personally identifying details such as, but not limited to, the server they visitors are logged onto, the geographic location of the ISP they use, the type of browser they use, and their IP address. This information is obtained solely for statistical purposes. 

**Use of Information:**

3DStats.com does not sell any collected information to third parties. 

**Contacting Us:**

If you have any additional questions about 3DStats.com's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at [privacy@3dstats.com](mailto:privacy@3dstats.com).
